Yuji Oshiro

yujioshiro.com • linkedin.com/yujioshiro Lake Forest, CA • (949) 309-6900 • <u>iamyujioshiro@gmail.com</u>

Summary

Computer Science student working towards transferring to a 4-year University for the Fall 2022 semester while obtaining an associate degree in Computer Science. I have participated in several hackathons building web/mobile applications and am currently working on strengthening my JavaScript/web development skills.

Education

Currently attending Irvine Valley College, but will be transferring to CSULB this upcoming Fall as a Junior pursuing my bachelor's in computer science.

I have taken C/C++, Intro to Python, and calculus courses. I have also completed the Foundations course for an open-source web development curriculum called The Odin Project and am going through the Full Stack JavaScript course in my free time, which strengthens HTML/CSS/JS skills and teaches React and Node.js.

Experience

CodePath.org [iOS Tech Fellow]

October 2021 - May 2022

- Tech lead for CodePath.org iOS course
- · Teach programming fundamentals to students using iOS and Swift
- Code review and debug student's code
- Facilitate and manage team building within the class and community building on campus

Taco Bell [Level 1 Service Desk Analyst]

February 2021 – July 2021

- Provide technical assistance to stores with software and hardware issues
- Identify issues and provide accurate troubleshooting to resolve problems
- Act as first line analysis within the service desk chain to resolve issues quickly and accurately or escalate with proper notes as needed
- Manage and prioritize work activities with minimal supervision to ensure field operations continue without interruption

The Darkroom [Assistant Production Manager]

May 2018 – March 2020

- Oversee a team of lab technicians in the processing of film
- Ensure quality of work remains consistent from order to order
- Take note of any issues with machines related to production and repair when necessary, or report it to the responsible party

Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, C/C++, Java, Python, Swift
- Software: Atom, Git/GitHub, Xcode, Android Studio
- Hardware: Comfortable working with PCs, Macs, and mobile devices